http://www.quartz-tsl.com/about-us/privacy-policy

Privacy Notice
Quartz Technical Services Ltd is committed to protecting the privacy and security of your personal information.
This privacy notice describes how we collect and use personal information about you during and after your working relationship with us, in accordance with the General Data Protection Regulations (GDPR). This may be data collected when you use our website or any other form of communication such as telephone, e-mail or post.
What is the purpose of this document?
Quartz Technical Services Limited is a "data controller". This means that we are responsible for deciding how we hold and use personal information about you. We are required under data protection legislation to notify you of the information contained in this privacy notice.
We may update this notice at any time.
Data protection principles
We will comply with data protection law. This says that the personal information we hold about you must be:
1. Used lawfully, fairly and in a transparent way.
2. Collected only for valid purposes that we have clearly explained to you and not used in any way that is incompatible with those purposes.
3. Relevant to the purposes we have told you about and limited only to those purposes.
4. Accurate and kept up to date.
5. Kept only as long as necessary for the purposes we have told you about.
6. Kept securely.
The kind of information we hold about you
Your Name
Your Job Title
Your company name.
Your company e-mail address.
Your company invoice address
Your company delivery address
Your company phone number
How is your personal information collected?
By telephone
By e-mail
By online form completion
How we will use information about you
We will only use your personal information when the law allows us to. Most commonly, we will use your personal information in the following circumstances:
To process your order, manage your account and to provide you with support for our products.
To send information by e-mail about the products and services we think may be of interest to you, wherever possible we make sure any information we send is targeted and relevant.
We may also contact you by phone to offer products and services we think may be of service to you.
We do not share your information for marketing purposes with any third party.
We will keep your data safe and secure for as long as necessary or according to any instructions from you.
If you fail to provide personal information
If you fail to provide certain information when requested, we may not be able to perform the contract we have entered into with you (such as delivering our products to you), or we may be prevented from complying with our legal obligations (such as to ensure the health and safety of our workers).
Change of purpose
We will only use your personal information for the purposes for which we collected it, unless we reasonably consider that we need to use it for another reason and that reason is compatible with the original purpose
Data sharing
We may have to share your data with third parties, including third-party service providers.
Delivery companies, so we can get your order to you.
Data security
We have put in place measures to protect the security of your information. Details of these measures are available upon request.
Data retention
We will only retain your personal information for as long as necessary to fulfil the purposes we collected it for, including for the purposes of satisfying any legal, accounting, or reporting requirements
Rights of access, correction, erasure, and restriction
Your duty to inform us of changes
It is important that the personal information we hold about you is accurate and current. Please keep us informed if your personal information changes during your working relationship with us. Under certain circumstances, by law you have the right to:
Request access to your personal information. This enables you to receive a copy of the personal information we hold about you and to check that we are lawfully processing it.
Request correction of the personal information that we hold about you. This enables you to have any incomplete or inaccurate information we hold about you corrected.
Request erasure of your personal information. This enables you to ask us to delete or remove personal information where there is no good reason for us continuing to process it. You also have the right to ask us to delete or remove your personal information where you have exercised your right to object to processing.
Object to processing of your personal information where we are relying on a legitimate interest (or those of a third party) and there is something about your particular situation which makes you want to object to processing on this ground. You also have the right to object where we are processing your personal information for direct marketing purposes.
Request the restriction of processing of your personal information. This enables you to ask us to suspend the processing of personal information about you, for example if you want us to establish its accuracy or the reason for processing it.
Request the transfer of your personal information to another party.
Right to withdraw consent
In the limited circumstances where you may have provided your consent to the collection, processing and transfer of your personal information for a specific purpose, you have the right to withdraw your consent for that specific processing at any time.  Once we have received notification that you have withdrawn your consent, we will no longer process your information for the purpose or purposes you originally agreed to, unless we have another legitimate basis for doing so in law.
Changes to this privacy notice
We reserve the right to update this privacy notice at any time, and we will provide you with a new privacy notice when we make any substantial updates.
If you have any questions about this privacy notice, please contact
By Telephone: 01455 824646
By email: sales@quartz-tsl.com
By Post: Quartz Technical Services Limited, Stokes Industrial Park, Merrylees, Near Desford, Leicestershire, LE9 9FE.
The Sidings,
Registered office: Quartz Technical Services Ltd, Stokes Industrial Park, Merrylees, Near Desford, Leicestershire LE9 9FE, United Kingdom |
Registered in England: 02091568 |
Site by Verto
